[{"answer": "Antwort 0", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113001", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 0", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 1", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113057", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 1", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 2", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113074", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 2", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 3", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113088", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 3", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 5", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113134", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 5", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 6", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113150", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 6", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 9", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113164", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 9", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 4", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113177", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 4", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 7", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113190", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 7", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": true, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 8", "date": "2018-12-29 17:49:29.113203", "chunk": 0, "question": "Frage 8", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 10", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672672", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 10", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 11", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672740", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 11", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 12", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672765", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 12", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 13", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672785", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 13", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 14", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672804", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 14", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 15", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672822", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 15", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 16", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672840", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 16", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 17", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672857", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 17", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 18", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672874", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 18", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 19", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:29.672891", "chunk": 1, "question": "Frage 19", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 20", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.876892", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 20", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 21", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.876957", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 21", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 22", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.876980", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 22", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 23", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877000", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 23", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 24", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877018", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 24", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 25", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877035", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 25", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 26", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877051", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 26", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 27", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877067", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 27", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 28", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877084", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 28", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}, {"answer": "Antwort 29", "date": "2018-12-27 19:28:40.877101", "chunk": 2, "question": "Frage 29", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "learned": false, "info2": ""}]